Hello.
こんにちは
I guess it's quite a long time.
結構ぶりなんですかね
It feels like a long time ago.
久々な感じ
I agree.
そうですね
About half a year or so.
半年とかもそれぐらい
It's been quite a while.
結構経ちましたね
I agree.
そうですね
What were you doing up until then?
それまで何されてたんですか?
Like going out.
出かけに行ったりとか
You like games.
ゲーム好きなんですね
Have you become a bit more mature?
ちょっと大人っぽくなりました?
a bit.
少し
Has anything changed?
何か変わったことがありました?
Where did you go?
どこ行ったとか
Aren't you going out?
出かけてないんですか?
I don't really go out much.
特にあんまり出かけてないです
It's like going out somewhere that you can normally go to.
何か普通に行ける範囲ぐらいの出かけみたいな
What about traveling?
旅行とかは?
About 3 months ago.
3ヶ月前ぐらいです
Did you go?
行ったんですか?
3 months ago.
3ヶ月前は
Where did you go?
どこ行ったんですか?
At that time, I went to Sendai.
その時は仙台行きました
Sendai?
仙台?
Why back to Sendai?
なんでまた仙台に?
I went there because I wanted to eat beef tongue.
牛タン食べたくて行きました
Beef tongue is delicious.
牛タンおいしいんですね
delicious.
おいしい
That's nice.
いいですね
After all, when you travel, you want to go out to eat, right?
やっぱり旅行はご飯食べに行きたいって感じなんですか?
I agree.
そうですね
Rice is the best.
ご飯が一番ですね
ご飯一番
Do you like eating?
食べるの好きなんですか?
I like it.
好きです
The style is nice, isn't it?
スタイルいいですよね
Don't you gain weight by eating?
食べて太らないんですか?
I'll gain weight.
太ります
Are you fat?
太ってるんですか?
Do you exercise to get back on track?
運動して戻したりとかしてますか?
It's pretty much like that with vegetables.
野菜とか結構そういう感じ
I'm eating healthy.
健康に食事してます
As much as possible.
なるべく
I only eat a lot when I travel.
旅行する時だけ、そういう時だけガッツリ食べます
I eat a lot.
ガッツリ食べます
Does that mean you're restrained in general?
普段も節制してるってことですか?
yes.
はい
The secret to the bottle?
ビンの秘訣ですか?
that's right.
そうです
What about games?
ゲームの方はどうなんですか?
Have you been doing this a lot lately?
最近ずっとやってるんですか?
I agree.
そうですね
I've been doing it a lot lately.
最近ずっとやってて
What are you doing?
何やってるんですっけ?
This is Epecos.
エペコスです
Popular?
人気の?
It's popular.
人気です
What do you like about it?
どういう所が好きなんですか?
What do you mean, it's fun to meet each other?
どういう所、打ち合うのが楽しいというか
Is it better to defeat it?
倒すのがいい?
I agree.
そうですね
There's something like a rank.
なんか、ランクとかあるんですよね
I agree.
そうですね
What do you think?
どう思いますか?
Master?
マスター?
I told you.
言ったんですけど
What is the position of master?
マスターってどういう位置付けなんですか?
It's faster to count from the top, so it's second from the top.
上から数うと早いんで、上から2番目です
Number two, it's still there.
2番目、まだあるんですね
There's more.
まだあります
What was it last time?
前回は何だったんですか?
Last time it was Diamond 2.
前回はダイヤ2です
From there, it seems like one ball goes up and another one goes up.
そっから、1球いってまたもう1個上がるみたいな
that's right.
そうです
That's amazing, Master.
すごいっすね、マスター
Not much.
あんまり
Because it's mobile.
モバイルなんで
Is there something different about mobile?
モバイル、また何か違うのがあるんですか?
I think it's harder to rank up on PC.
PCの方がランク上がりづらいかなっていう
But wouldn't mastering it on mobile be amazing?
でも、モバイルでマスターもすごいんじゃないですか?
The settings on mobile are probably weak.
モバイルは多分、設定が弱いんで
setting?
設定?
The settings are so much better than the PC,
設定が、PCよりは全然勝てるようになってるんで、
I think it's easy.
楽だと思います
What else did you do just now, Master?
あとは今、その上何でしたっけ、マスター?
It's Predator.
プレデターです
Are you trying to become a Predator?
プレデター目指してやってるんですか?
that's right.
そうです
Even if it's a mess, it's good.
めちゃくちゃでも上手いですね
I tried my best.
やりこみました
Because if you do too much, you won't be good at it.
だって、いっぱいやれば上手くない
It's not like you're going up in rank, right?
ランク上がってくるってわけじゃないでしょ?
I agree.
そうですね
If we don't win, we won't move up.
勝たないとやっぱり上がらないです
It's like a winning pattern, or some advice for people who are just starting out.
なんか必勝パターンというか、今始めた人に何かアドバイスみたい
Do you have any?
な のあるんですか?
After all, the actions of the three people are the most important.
やっぱり3人の行動が一番大事なんで、
The best way to win is to use a voicer and tell one enemy that there is one.
ボイシャーつけて、敵1個にいるよとか教えてあげるのが一番勝ち
I think it's easy.
や すいと思います
Is it a command tower or a team of three people?
指令塔なんですか、3人のチームというんですか?
I agree.
そうですね
After all, I have to add voicing.
やっぱりボイシャーつけないと
How do you feel, usually?
どんな感じなんですか、普段?
Usually, normally.
普段、普通に
Are you the one who gives instructions?
指示をする方なんですか?
No, that's right.
いや、そうですね
There's an enemy.
敵いるよとか
Does it feel like someone is pulling you?
誰かが引っ張るような感じなんですか、
When do you do that kind of voice?
そういうボイシャーをするときは?
It depends on the character.
それはキャラクターによりますね
Any skills?
なんかスキルとか?
that's right.
そうです
If you don't have a character that draws you in, it will be difficult to defeat him.
引っ張る感じのキャラクターじゃないと倒しづらいんで
What type are you usually?
どういうタイプなんですか、普段は?
Usually, I don't really go to battle,
普段は、あんま戦いに行くというよりかは、
What do you mean?
なんていうんだろう
Subsidy?
補助とか?
I agree.
そうですね
There may be more assistance.
補助とかの方が多いかもしれないです
The support is good.
サポートよくなんですね
that's right.
そうです
What is that, like recovery?
それは何ですか、回復とかなんですか?
Hmm, I don't know what to say.
うーんと、なんていうんだろう
I have a lot of skills, but
スキルが結構付いているんですけど、
It depends on that.
それによりますね
It's a little complicated, and it's not an easy level type.
ちょっと複雑なんですね、簡単に言えるレベルタイプでもないです
From.
から ね
sorry.
すみません
a little bit,
ちょっと、
I would like to see a different side of you again today.
また 今日、また違った一面を見せてもらいたいですけど、
What kind of people are there?
どんな人がいます?
How does it feel?
どんな感じですか?
What does it look like?
どんな感じに見えます?
Well, what does it feel like?
えっ、どんな感じ?
Are you handsome?
イケメンですか?
perhaps.
多分
Are you okay, man?
大丈夫ですか、あの人?
it's okay.
大丈夫です
Please give me a call.
ちょっと呼んでみてください
nice to meet you.
初めまして
He's handsome.
イケメンです
I've been looking at it for a while now, but her boobs aren't that beautiful.
さっきから見てたんですけど、すごいおっぱい綺麗じゃない
Is it?
ですか?
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Can I have your spine tightened?
背 筋ピッとしてもらっていい?
Look, it's amazing.
ほら、すごいよ
Hey, what do you say?
ねえ、言われますよく?
yes.
はい
The style is nice.
スタイルいいっすね
Because, look, if you look at it from below,
だってほら、下からこう見たらさ、
Her boobs are so big I can't see her face.
おっぱいが大きくて顔見えないもん
It's nice to have a good laugh with Iason.
笑ってくれてアイソンもいいし
Okay, wait, is it okay to do it like that?
こうだな、ちょっと、そうやっていいっすか?
I've touched the breasts of more women than I can count.
数えきれないくらい多くの女性のおっぱい触ったんですけど、
It's breasts on the day when three fingers enter.
3本の指に入る日におっぱいですよ
Is there a good way to touch this?
これ、どんな風に触れるのがいいとかありますか?
Hmm, that's how I feel now.
うーん、今の感じね
Like this?
こんな感じ?
Hmm, I'm happy.
うーん、嬉しいっすね
A pretty beautiful valley.
結構綺麗な谷間
Everyone who passes by will see this, right?
これ、すれ違う人みんな見るでしょ?
So beautiful.
すごい綺麗
I want to go inside this.
入りたいっすね、この中に
Just try it last time.
ちょっと前回もやってみて
Ah, nice.
あ、いいね
This is a deodorizing vehicle, this one.
これ、脱臭乗ってるんだよ、これ
I don't know.
知らないね
I fall asleep like this.
寝ちゃったりするんですよ、こうやって
That's right, you look at me with sad eyes.
そう いうの、切ない目で見てるね
It's unbearable.
たまんないっすね
Can I ask you to help me?
手伝ってみてもらっていい?
Help me, myself.
手伝って、自分で
Ah, yes, yes.
あ、そうそうそう
Wow, this is erotic.
うわ、これエロいなぁ
I like this tile.
こいつ、タイルいいね
It's in this person.
こいつの人に入ってるね
yeah?
ん?
Don't close it.
閉じれないで
why?
なんで?
Great, it's closed.
すげぇ閉じるじゃん
why?
なんで?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
what up?
どうした?
It's beautiful, it's beautiful.
綺麗だよ、綺麗
So beautiful.
めっちゃ綺麗
I'll hide it.
隠すね
But the more I try to hide it, the more people want to see what I do.
でもね、隠そうつればすることを見たがるのが、
Make it a man, right?
男にするんだよね
Do you know?
知ってる?
Let's show it to people outside.
外の人に見せよう
I wonder if everyone is watching?
みんな、見てるかな?
On the side.
脇をね
Aren't you ashamed of your breasts?
おっぱいは恥ずかしくない?
Well, the armpits are more embarrassing.
え、脇の方が恥ずかしい
That's right.
そうなんだね
Women's psychology is complex.
女性心理って、やっぱ複雑だね
Take a look.
見てみて
Those people walking by, those apartment buildings.
そ この歩いてる人とかさ、あのマンションのさ、
There are some places where the curtains are open.
カーテン開いてるとこあるじゃん
I'm looking at you, boobs.
見てるからね、おっぱい
Your lips are really nice.
唇はすごいいいよね
oh yeah
そうそう
yes.
そう
Is this how you talk?
こう やって喋るでしょ?
Just try talking like that.
ちょっとあれみたいに喋ってみてよ
Don't you use your hands?
手使ったりしない?
You can do it like this, right?
こうやってもついでしょ
That's terrible.
やばいな
It's so prickly.
ちくちやろいね
You're so stubborn.
かたくなにわきやがるね
That's amazing.
すごいね
so?
そんなに?
Are there that many?
そんなにあるの?
Why is it so beautiful?
なんでこんなにきれいなのに?
I wonder why.
なんでなんだろうね
Maybe it's because I can't see it.
見られないからかな
Is that so?
そういうこと?
Yeah.
うん
Well, I definitely want to see it.
そりゃあ、ぜひ見たいね
Well, on the other hand, what about this one?
え、逆にじゃあこっちは?
No, it's about the same here.
いや、こっちも同じくらいか
real?
ほんと?
I guess I should go then.
じゃあいっちゃおうかな
It's easy to see, it's a mobile phone.
見やすいようにさ、携帯じゃん
It's really easy to see, thanks.
すごい見やすいよ、おかげで
Shouldn't you be a little less scolded?
もうちょっとあさくされなくない?
Wouldn't it be embarrassing if I did it myself?
自分でやったら恥ずかしないかな
I can't help it.
しょうがない
Where to put it out.
出すところ
Look bright.
明るいように見て
I'm looking closely at it in a bright place.
明るいところでさ、がっつり見てるよ
Try putting some effort into it.
ちょっと 力入れてみて
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
One more time.
もう一回
Apply or remove force.
力入れたり抜いたり
nice.
いいね
It's really beautiful, but have you taken care of it?
すごいきれいだけどさ、なんか手入れしてんの?
Haven't you been drinking?
飲みましてないの?
It's so beautiful
めちゃくちゃきれいだ
Yo.
よ
Put it away.
や っぱおけ
Yes, get on your hips.
そう、お腰につきだしって
Stop it for a second.
ちょっとやめてさ
Yeah, stop it.
そう、やめて
Stop it for a second.
ちょっとやめてよ
The one with a tongue full of sores.
舌いっぱいのがしたやつ
Try licking it.
ぺるぺるしてみて
Yeah, okay.
そう、いいよ
Get down on your knees.
ひざわずになって
Rest?
休みる?
oh
お
It starts to touch my waist.
腰 につきだし
That's amazing, you remember it.
すごいね、覚えてんだね
The sides are doing well.
ちゃんと脇がやがるな
That's amazing.
すごいな
You're calm.
冷静だな